SADIG AKHUND

COMPUTER ENGINEER, IT EVANGELIST, STUBBORN ARGUMENT SEEKER, CURIOUS EXPLORER

ABOUT ME

Adaptable Computer Engineer with some work experience currently leveling up education with MSc. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of advanced technology, electronics, engineering, and programming skills to successfully fill that vacant spot at your company. Frequently praised as hard-working as well as honest, can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

LANGUAGES

English Full Professional / IELTS 7.5

Russian Native or Bilingual Prof.

German Beginner

Azerbaijani/Turkish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

TECHNICAL

Proficient Level:

Java / Kotlin, C/C++, PL/SQL, Python

Experience with:

Java Spring Boot, Java Swing, Kali / Linux, ASP.Net Core

More:

Portfolio:

Assembly(ARM), ROS, VHDL, Game Development, Android, Arduino, C#

CONTACT

Address: 18th Tabriz Street.

Baku, Azerbaijan, 1008

Mobile: +994 (70) 318 59 49

Email: sadigaxund@gmail.com



sakhund.netlify.ap

EDUCATION

BSc in Computer Engineering

ADA University - 3.47 CGPA

09/2017 - 06/2021

- Advanced Networks
- Cyber Security
- Database Systems
- Software Engineering

Baku, Azerbaijan

- Computer Architecture
- Algorithms & Data Structures
- Electronics & IC Design
- Mobile Robotics

BSc in Computer Engineering

METU (ODTÜ) University – Exchange Program

02/2019 – 06/2019 Ankara, Turkey

Cyber Security Training

Ministry of Education

12/2020 - 05/2021

Baku, Azerbaijan

- Ethical HackingWeb application pen-testina
- Incident Response & HandlingThreat Hunting & Forensics

MSc in Computer Science and Data Analytics

ADA University / George Washington University

09/2021 – Present

Baku, Azerbaijan / Washington DC, USA

EXPERIENCE

Internship

ATL Tech LLC

Role: Software Development intern. C#. Asp.net Core

May 2021

Baku, Azerbaijan

Internship

Sumaks Technologies LTD

Role: Hardware development and Production intern. Embedded C.
2019 - 2020

Baku, Azerbaijan

Volunteer

Azerbaijan Red Crescent Society

Role: Spreading governmental aid packages for those who are elderly, or who are otherwise unable to meet their needs.

2018 - 2021 Narimanov district, Baku, Azerbaijan

Counselling, Trained Tutor

ADA University, Student Academic Support Services

Role: Assisting students to overcome their academic challenges.

2018 - 2019 Baku, Azerbaijan